http://www.rhosonics.nl/privacy-policy/

HomeProductsApplicationsCasesNewsCompanyContactSearchEnglishChineseEspañolFrenchLoginHomeProductsApplicationsCasesNewsCompanyContactHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyYour privacy is critically important to us. At Rhosonics Analytical B.V. we have a few fundamental principles:We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.It is Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Rhosonics Analytical B.V. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s visitors use its website.Rhosonics Analytical B.V. also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Rhosonics Analytical B.V. only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s websites choose to interact with Rhosonics Analytical B.V. in ways that require Rhosonics Analytical B.V. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Rhosonics Analytical B.V. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide an email address. Those who engage with Rhosonics Analytical B.V. are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal information required to process those engagements. In each case, Rhosonics Analytical B.V. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Rhosonics Analytical B.V. . Rhosonics Analytical B.V. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Rhosonics Analytical B.V. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s behalf or to provide services available at Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Rhosonics Analytical B.V.’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Rhosonics Analytical B.V. will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Rhosonics Analytical B.V. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Rhosonics Analytical B.V. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Rhosonics Analytical B.V., third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Rhosonics Analytical B.V. website and have supplied your email address, Rhosonics Analytical B.V. may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Rhosonics Analytical B.V. and our products. We primarily use our blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Rhosonics Analytical B.V. takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
